<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://davegonzalez.github.io/feed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-18T16:54:45.242Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://davegonzalez.github.io/feed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://davegonzalez.github.io/feed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple planning MacBook Pro with 16-core GPU, Mac Pro with 128 GPU cores]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765693</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765693"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg's sources spill core counts and more on the next wave of Macs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music Lossless: What Devices are Supported?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-lossless&amp;post_date=1621365456/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-lossless/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple in June 2021 is adding new Lossless and Hi-Res Lossless tiers to Apple Music, but so far, it's a bit confusing trying to determine which devices support ‌Apple Music‌'s Lossless Audio and which devices do not.




Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel for more videos.


This guide covers everything that we know so far about Lossless Audio, and we'll be updating it as we learn more after the new feature launches.



What is Lossless Audio?


Apple is upgrading its entire streaming musi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juli Clover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Award-Winning iPhone Camera App Halide Expands to iPad With New 'Pro View']]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/halide-camera-app-now-available-on-ipad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/halide-camera-app-now-available-on-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just three days before the new iPad Pro begins arriving to customers, the developers of award-winning iPhone camera app Halide have announced the release of an iPad app, complete with a custom user interface that takes advantage of the larger screen.





To keep the viewfinder minimally obscured, the iPad app has an expandable "honeycomb" of controls next to the shutter button for manually adjusting shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and more. Other key features are readily reachable at the edges of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Rossignol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Working on High-End Mac Mini With Additional Ports and More Powerful Chip From Next-Gen MacBook Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/apple-working-on-high-end-mac-mini/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/apple-working-on-high-end-mac-mini/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T15:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is working on a high-end version of the Mac mini, featuring a more powerful Apple silicon chip and extra ports, according to Bloomberg's Mark Gurman.





In a wide-reaching report, Gurman explained that Apple is developing a more powerful version of the ‌Mac mini‌, positioned as a high-end version of the current M1 model. The new ‌Mac mini‌ is expected to use the same chip as the next-generation MacBook Pro.



The next-generation MacBook Pro models are expected to feature an improved versi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hartley Charlton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another media acquisition? This one would involve Amazon, MGM, and ~$9B]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765675</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765675"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T15:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does this at least mean we can watch No Time to Die at home soon?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Mattise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive Deals: Get Up to 52% Off Popular Anker Portable Batteries, Wireless Chargers, and Other Accessories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/exclusive-deals-popular-anker-batteries/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/exclusive-deals-popular-anker-batteries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T15:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we've partnered up with Anker to offer our readers a collection of new discount codes on wireless chargers, portable batteries, and wall chargers. In this sale you'll find up to 52 percent off select Anker accessories, with prices starting at just $17.99 for the company's MagSafe-compatible Magnetic Wireless Charger.



Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.



There a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mitchel Broussard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple TV Color Balance Feature May Make Image Quality and Colors Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/apple-tv-color-balance-quality-colors-worse/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/apple-tv-color-balance-quality-colors-worse/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple TV's Color Balance calibration feature may make color accuracy and image quality worse on some TVs, tests have found (via AFTVnews).





Professional television calibrator Vincent Teoh, who runs the YouTube channel HDTVTest, put the ‌Apple TV‌'s color calibration feature to the test on a range of popular TVs in a recent video.



The ‌Apple TV‌'s Color Calibration debuted in tvOS 14.5 and iOS 14.5, giving users the ability to hold an iPhone with Face ID near their TV and, after tapping a no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hartley Charlton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SteelSeries Offers up to Four Months of Apple Arcade Free With Nimbus+ Controller [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/four-months-apple-arcade-nimbus-controller/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/four-months-apple-arcade-nimbus-controller/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SteelSeries, the makers of popular gaming controllers for Apple devices, has today announced that all purchases of the Nimbus+ Wireless Gamepad Controller will come with up to four free months of Apple Arcade.





The SteelSeries Nimbus+ Wireless Gamepad Controller delivers a "console-quality experience" with ‌Apple Arcade‌'s library of games.



Iterating on the original Nimbus controller, the Nimbus+ Wireless Gamepad Controller features an ergonomic design, ultra-responsive triggers and buttons…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hartley Charlton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next MacBook Air Will Feature Faster Apple Silicon Chip With Up to 10 Graphics Cores]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/next-macbook-air-faster-apple-silicon-chip/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/next-macbook-air-faster-apple-silicon-chip/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is working on a high-end version of the MacBook Air that will feature an improved iteration of the current M1 Apple silicon chip, featuring improved graphics, but the same number of high efficiency, and high performance cores, according to Bloomberg's Mark Gurman.





Apple updated its 13-inch ‌MacBook Air‌ alongside the 13-inch MacBook Pro and Mac mini with the ‌M1‌ Apple silicon chip in November. Bloomberg says that this new ‌MacBook Air‌, which could launch as soon as the end of this year, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sami Fathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M1 iMac Reviews: Impressively Fast With Long-Awaited Redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/review/m1-imac&amp;post_date=1621354704/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/m1-imac/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The embargo has lifted on reviews of Apple's new 24-inch iMac, powered by the same M1 chip that debuted in the 13-inch MacBook Pro, MacBook Air, and Mac mini last year. We've gathered up impressions of the colorful new computer below.





The most striking aspect of the new iMac is its long-awaited redesign, with an ultra-thin 11.5mm chassis that comes in up to seven vibrant colors, including green, yellow, orange, pink, purple, blue, and silver. The Verge's Monica Chin said the new colors have gener…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Rossignol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad Launches Updated Titanium and Steel Bands for Apple Watch, Priced From $149.95]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/nomad-updated-bands-apple-watch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/nomad-updated-bands-apple-watch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad today announced updated versions of its Titanium and Steel Bands for the Apple Watch (42mm or 44mm sizes only). The company said that the new versions of its existing accessories include multiple improvements that result in a lighter metal band that retains its durability.





Other improvements include new custom 316L stainless steel lugs, 100% color matched to the rest of the band. Nomad added an ultra-slim clasp that stays closed using N52 magnets, and it also allows for easier opening and a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mitchel Broussard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: M1 iMac Unboxing Videos and First Impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/m1-imac-unboxing-videos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/m1-imac-unboxing-videos/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 24-inch iMac with the M1 chip is now available to order and set to begin arriving with customers starting on Friday, May 21.





The iMac features a 24-inch 4.5K Retina Display, Apple's custom silicon ‌M1‌ chip for improved performance, a new, ultra-slim design, and is available in a range of color options.



Ahead of the arrival of orders this Friday, Apple has provided some YouTube channels and media outlets with an early look at its new Apple silicon-powered desktop computer. We've rounde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hartley Charlton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg: Apple Silicon Mac Pro May Feature Up to 32 High Performance Cores, 128 Core Option for Graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/bloomberg-mac-pro-32-high-performance-cores/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/bloomberg-mac-pro-32-high-performance-cores/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is working on an updated model of its Mac Pro that may feature an Apple silicon chip with as many as 32 high performance cores, and a 128 core option for graphics, according to a new report from Bloomberg's Mark Gurman. 





Bloomberg has reported in the past that Apple is working on an updated Mac Pro that will feature an Apple silicon chip rather than an Intel processor. Today's new report echoes a similar story but offers more details on the performance of this upcoming high-end Mac. 


…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sami Fathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distribution and Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://stratechery.com/?p=5889</id>
        <link href="https://stratechery.com/2021/distribution-and-demand/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Distribution on the Internet is free; what matters is controlling demand. AT&T and Verizon didn't understand the distinction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned MacBook Pro Models With 10-Core Apple Silicon Chip Said to Launch as Early as This Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/macbook-pro-64gb-ram-summer-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/macbook-pro-64gb-ram-summer-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple plans to launch new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with an improved iteration of the M1 chip as early as this summer, according to Bloomberg's Mark Gurman. The new chip is said to include a 10-core CPU with eight high-performance cores and two energy-efficient cores, with 16-core or 32-core GPU options.





Gurman said the next-generation Apple silicon chip will also support up to 64GB of memory compared to the current maximum of 16GB. This would be in line with the current Intel-based …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Rossignol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify HiFi Icon Spotted in Mobile App Suggests Imminent Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/spotify-lossless-hifi-option-spotted-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/spotify-lossless-hifi-option-spotted-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify in February announced plans to introduce a new "HiFi" premium tier sometime in 2021, and while the company declined to offer a date, there's reason to believe a launch could be imminent, especially in the wake of Apple Music's lossless tier announcement on Monday.





In a timely discovery, hints of Spotify's lossless HiFi audio streaming service have again been spotted this week by Reddit user themonarc, who shared their finding with the accompanying image above.  



According to the Re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hardwick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New iMac, iPad Pro, and Apple TV 4K Available at Apple Stores Starting May 21]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/new-imac-ipad-pro-apple-tv-may-21/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/new-imac-ipad-pro-apple-tv-may-21/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple today confirmed that the new 24-inch iMac, iPad Pro, and updated Apple TV 4K will be available for customers in Apple Stores and retail locations around the world on Friday, May 21. Pre-orders for the products began earlier last month, and Apple previously said the new products will be available in the second half of May.





The new ‌iPad Pro‌ features the M1 Apple silicon chip, first introduced in the MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, and Mac mini last November. The larger 12.9-inch ‌iPad Pro‌ also f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sami Fathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McLaren goes with a clean-sheet chassis and engine for Artura supercar]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765657</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765657"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a new carbon-fiber monocoque and a 120-degree V6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demeo is the best multiplayer, virtual-reality D&D clone ever made]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763983</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763983"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issues aside, it already feels like sharing a real-life dice-and-minis table with friends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music for Android Reportedly Won't Support Dolby Atmos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/apple-music-android-no-dolby-atmos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/apple-music-android-no-dolby-atmos/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T09:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music on Android devices will not include Dolby Atmos support when Apple launches Spatial Audio on the streaming service in June. That's the claim from MySmartPrice, which says it received confirmation from Apple India that the sound technology would not be crossing the divide between Apple and Android ecosystems.





For anyone confused by all the audio nomenclature that's been bandied about since the ‌Apple Music‌ announcement on Monday, Dolby Atmos is based on surround sound technology that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hardwick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 14.6 RC Introduces New Shazam App Clip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/ios-14-6-rc-shazam-app-clip/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/ios-14-6-rc-shazam-app-clip/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T08:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the iOS and iPadOS 14.6 RC update that was released yesterday, Apple has introduced a new Shazam App Clip, which now allows users to find and identify a song using the new iOS 14 feature, instead of being redirected to the Shazam website or app. 





Apple introduced App Clips with ‌iOS 14‌ in June of last year as a small, mini-app that can run on a device, without a user needing to download an app from the App Store. There are multiple ways to activate an App Clip, including a specially d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sami Fathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned MacBook Pro Models Still on Track for 2021 Launch, But Supplies Likely to Be Constrained into Next Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/redesigned-macbook-pro-launch-limited-supply/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/18/redesigned-macbook-pro-launch-limited-supply/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T08:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volume production of the redesigned 16-inch MacBook Pro with Apple silicon and a mini-LED display is set to begin in the first quarter of 2022, while mass production of the smaller and new 14-inch MacBook Pro will begin in the fourth quarter of this year, according to industry sources cited in a paywalled DigiTimes report.





Yesterday, DigiTimes posted a preview of a story reporting that the launch of the redesigned MacBook Pros could be delayed until next year. Now, the full report offers more con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sami Fathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's New 24-Inch iMac Shown Off in Early Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/17/24-inch-imac-unboxing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/17/24-inch-imac-unboxing/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T03:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update: The early unboxing video was taken down, but other unboxing and first impression videos are now available.





The new 24-inch iMac doesn't officially launch until this Friday, May 21, but an early unboxing of the machine has been shared on YouTube.




The ‌iMac‌ unboxing video was made private subsequent to this story.


The video from Gadget Guy is in Cantonese, but it offers an up-close look at the yellow version of the ‌iMac‌ including how the machine and its color-matched accessor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Slivka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden pledges to share 20 million COVID-19 vaccine doses with the world]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765579</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765579"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 20 million will be in addition to 60 million AstraZeneca doses already pledged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AirPods Max Won't Directly Support Lossless Apple Music Over Lightning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/17/airpods-max-no-direct-lossless-lightning-support/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/17/airpods-max-no-direct-lossless-lightning-support/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today, we confirmed that AirPods, AirPods Pro, and AirPods Max will not support lossless audio over Bluetooth because of Bluetooth limitations, and it turns out there's no direct wired lossless option for the ‌AirPods Max‌ either.





Apple's ‌AirPods Max‌ headphones are equipped with a Lightning port, but it is limited to analog sources and will not natively support digital audio formats in wired mode. 



Apple told The Verge that when a 24-bit/48 kHz Apple Music lossless track is playe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juli Clover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Security Compromises in China Outlined in New Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/17/apple-security-compromises-china-icloud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/17/apple-security-compromises-china-icloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has been making concessions on privacy and security in order to continue building and selling its devices in China, according to an in-depth report from The New York Times.





The focal point of the report is Apple's decision to comply with a 2016 law that requires all personal information and data collected in China to be kept in China, which has led Apple to build a China data center and relocate Chinese customers' iCloud data to China, managed by a Chinese company.



Apple fought again…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juli Clover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s M1 is a fast CPU—but M1 Macs feel even faster due to QoS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765494</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765494"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howard Oakley did an excellent deep dive on M1 scheduling and performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music subscribers will get lossless and spatial audio for free next month]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765499</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765499"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T19:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New features will launch with iOS 14.6, macOS 11.4 in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocket Lab reviewing data after its second Electron failure in a year]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765439</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765439"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We deeply regret the loss of BlackSky's payload."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDC defends its abrupt reversal on masks after backlash from experts]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765479</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765479"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts question timing as CDC director says public pressure wasn’t a factor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T to spin off WarnerMedia, basically admitting giant merger was a mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765461</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765461"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WarnerMedia and Discovery to merge, and standalone AT&T will focus on broadband.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget multiple cameras—Sharp phone has one giant 1-inch camera sensor]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765409</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765409"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the biggest smartphone camera sensor ever—or at least tied.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City pays $350,000 after suing “hackers” for opening Dropbox link it sent them]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765448</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765448"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee mistakenly sent the link when replying to a records request.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not enough to trust science on vaccines—others have to as well]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765440</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765440"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personal trust and societal consensus have an additive effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Roblox’s definition of “games” is key to the Epic vs. Apple case]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765432</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765432"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The line between "game" and "experience" has major implications for iOS App Review.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From apes to birds, there are 65 animal species that “laugh”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765400</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765400"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laughter is spread widely across mammals and occurs in birds, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A brief look at electric vehicles from the dawn of the automobile age]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765381</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765381"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric vehicles were well represented during the early decades of the car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to look at the stack with gdb]]></title>
        <id>https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/17/how-to-look-at-the-stack-in-gdb/</id>
        <link href="https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/17/how-to-look-at-the-stack-in-gdb/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T09:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was chatting with someone yesterday and they mentioned that they don’t really
understand exactly how the stack works or how to look at it.
So here’s a quick walkthrough of how you can use gdb to look at the stack of a C
program. I think this would be similar for a Rust program, but I’m going to use
C because I find it a little simpler for a toy example and also you can do Terrible
Things in C more easily.
our test program
Here’s a simple C program that declares a few variables and reads two strings
from s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neutrons unlock the secrets of Antonie van Leeuwenhoek’s microscopes]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765022</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T21:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His most powerful microscope holds a lens likely made with Robert Hooke's 1678 recipe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2021 preview: Google resurrects Wear OS and Android tablets?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764606</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764606"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T13:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google I/O schedule promises to resurrect some long-dead form factors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop FOMO inspires a new wave of crypto pump-and-dumps]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765272</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765272"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T11:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discord groups promise big earnings  by manipulating the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The chip shortage is driving up tech prices–starting with TVs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765280</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765280"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T11:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some high-end televisions already cost 30% more than they did last summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Bangeman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare on the Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://stratechery.com/?p=5876</id>
        <link href="https://stratechery.com/2021/cloudflare-on-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is uniquely positioned to become a major player in an Internet 3.0 world, where politics matter more than economics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The OSI model doesn't map well to TCP/IP]]></title>
        <id>https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/11/what-s-the-osi-model-/</id>
        <link href="https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/11/what-s-the-osi-model-/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TCP/IP is the set of networking protocols that we use on the modern internet –
TCP, UDP, IP, ARP, ICMP, DNS, etc. When I talk about “networking”, I’m
basically always talking about TCP/IP.
Many explanations of TCP/IP start with something called the “OSI model”. I
don’t use the OSI model when explaining networking because when I first
started learning about internet networking I found all of the OSI model
explanations really confusing – it wasn’t clear to me at all how the OSI
model corresponded to TCP/IP.
S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market-Making on the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://stratechery.com/?p=5856</id>
        <link href="https://stratechery.com/2021/market-making-on-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T13:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More and more opportunities on the web come from market marking, not for advertisers, but for real goods and services paid for with real money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I put all of my comics online!]]></title>
        <id>https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/02/publishing-comics/</id>
        <link href="https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/02/publishing-comics/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-02T11:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! As you probably know, I write a lot of comics about programming, and I publish collections of them as zines you can buy at https://wizardzines.com.
I also usually post the comics on Twitter as I write them. But there are a lot of problems with just posting them to Twitter, like:
the pages are hard to find. For example, if you want to find the one on
socat, you can search twitter
and you’ll find it, but then you have to somehow magically guess what words I
used in the tweet, and also sort through a bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify’s Surprise]]></title>
        <id>https://stratechery.com/?p=5828</id>
        <link href="https://stratechery.com/2021/spotifys-surprise/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify's new subscription podcast offerings embrace the open ecosystem of podcasts in multiple ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast Subscriptions vs. the App Store]]></title>
        <id>https://stratechery.com/?p=5800</id>
        <link href="https://stratechery.com/2021/podcast-subscriptions-vs-the-app-store/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T14:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's new Podcast Subscription service is what the App Store should be: a great Apple experience competing for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>